{
    "subject": "resource/Milo_Andrus",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathDate",
    "object": "1893-06-19",
    "human_readable": "Milo Andrus died on June 19, 1893.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.962647020816803,
            "question": "What can we learn from the fact that Milo Andrus died on June 19th, 1893?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8879541754722595,
            "question": "What events might have happened in 1893 around the time of Milo Andrus's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8561235070228577,
            "question": "When did Milo Andrus die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7844274044036865,
            "question": "What year was Milo Andrus's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7232957482337952,
            "question": "Is June 19th a significant date in relation to Milo Andrus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6860737800598145,
            "question": "Who was Milo Andrus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5281692743301392,
            "question": "How significant was Milo Andrus's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4594568610191345,
            "question": "Are there any historical records about Milo Andrus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4333275556564331,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Milo Andrus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20899002254009247,
            "question": "Was June a common month for deaths in that era?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Milo Andrus died on June 19, 1893.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2292_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Milo Andrus?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2292_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical records about Milo Andrus?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2292_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How significant was Milo Andrus's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2292_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2292_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2292_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2292_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2292_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2292_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2292_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2292_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2292_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2292_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2292_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Milo died on June 19, 1893 in Oxford, Idaho,\" which directly supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}